popflash.site 2017-06-06

# PopFlash

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy discloses the online privacy practices for Denver Ghost, LLC and its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, predecessors, successors, partners, agents, officers, directors, employees, subcontractors, successors and assigns, third party suppliers of information and documents, attorneys, accountants, advertisers, product and service providers (collectively, “PopFlash” or “We” or “Us” or “Our”) and applies to the information We collect from persons accessing, using, and/or registering on PopFlash.site (the “Site”). By accessing, using, and/or registering on the Site, you, including your parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, predecessors, successors, partners, agents, officers, directors, employees, subcontractors, successors and assigns, third party suppliers of information and documents, attorneys, accountants, advertisers, product and service providers (“You” or “Your”) are consenting to the collection, storage, and disclosure of data as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is entered into in furtherance of Your use of any or all of PopFlash’s products (“Products”), services (“Services”), and the Site.

**Retention and Use of Personal Information**

PopFlash respects Your ability to make informed choices about the collection and use of Your personal information.“Personal information” is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify the person to whom such information pertains.Personal information may include but is not limited to Your name, date of birth, email address, region, country of residence, age, gender, Steam ID, Steam display name, Steam avatar, and matchmaking rank.

PopFlash also retains certain information automatically. Examples of automatic information We collect from You and analyze include the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect Your computer to the Internet, internet service provider, login, e-mail address, password, computer and other unique device identifiers, connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform, purchase history (which We sometimes aggregate with similar information from other users to create features), the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from Our Site, including date and time, cookie number, Services You viewed or searched for, pages You visited, and Your service history.We may use other tracking technologies, such as such as pixel tags and web beacons.During some visits, We may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

As PopFlash develops its Products and Services, PopFlash may contract with third party vendors that collect bank account information in order to process certain financial transactions, but no such bank account information is provided to or stored by PopFlash.

The Personal Information collected from the Site is stored indefinitely. PopFlash may use Your Personal Information to respond to requests for further information such as the availability and use of the Products and Services.We may share Your information with third parties who help deliver Our Products and Services to You.Examples include hosting Our web servers and processing payments via bank account wire. PopFlash does not and will not authorize third parties to duplicate, reuse, rent, or Your Personal Information, whether in hard-copy or electronic format. Your Personal Information will not be sold or rented to third parties. 

PopFlash shares Your Personal Information with companies We employ to provide services on Our behalf, such as information processing, fulfilling subscription orders, managing and enhancing data, designing software, providing user support and related services.We share only such information with these agents as We deem necessary in order for them to perform their functions. These companies are contractually obligated to protect Your Personal Information to the same degree as PopFlash does under this Privacy Policy and they may only use Your Personal Information as authorized herein or by You.

We release account and other Personal Information when We believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply Our Terms of Use Agreement and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of PopFlash, Our users, or others.This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.Information may be required to be shared with law enforcement or other governmental agencies with a legal right to require PopFlash to disclose such information.However, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing Your Personal Information for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.

PopFlash will ask for Your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy. 

If PopFlash is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, PopFlash will ensure the confidentiality of Your Personal Information and give You notice before Your Personal Information is transferred or is subject to a new privacy policy.

**Use of Your Likeness and Voice**

You understand that by playing in a match through PopFlash.site, you consent to the recording of certain Personal Information, including Your voice and gamer tag. Popflash reserves the right to use these recordings for both promotional and commercial purposes, in Popflash’s sole discretion.

**Security of Personal Information**

PopFlash takes appropriate measures to secure Your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, the Internet is an open system and We cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat those measures or use Your Personal Information for improper purposes.It is also important for You to protect against unauthorized access to Your password and to Your computer.Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**Service Providers**

PopFlash may engage service providers to perform certain functions and services.We may share Your Personal Information with such service providers subject to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy, and on the condition that the third parties use Your Personal Information only on behalf of PopFlash and pursuant to Our instructions.

**Cookies**

“Cookies” are identifiers We transfer to Your computer or device that allow Us to recognize Your browser or device and tell Us how and when pages in Our Site are visited and by how many people. We use cookies to carry information about usage from page to page through the Site. PopFlash does not use cookies to retrieve Personal Information about You from Your computer. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but You can usually change Your browser settings to refuse them. If You disable cookies, Your browser may experience some erratic behavior on some portions of the Site. Our advertising partners may transmit cookies to Your computer or device when You click on ads that appear on Our Site. This Privacy Policy does not cover cookies delivered to You by any of Our advertisers.

**Opt-In**

By using Our Site to submit Personal Information, You are granting PopFlash the right to use Your Personal Information as described above. If You desire to revoke this grant, please email us at: support@popflash.site and discontinue all use of this Site. Unless We receive Your request and use is discontinued, Your grant of a right to use Your information as described above will continue. In no event will We be responsible for recalling information We may have already provided to Our third-party associates should You choose to opt-out.

**Children**

It is not Our intention to collect Personal Information from anyone under 18 years of age. If You are under 18, You should not enter information on the Site and should ask a parent or legal guardian to do so for You. If You are under 13, We must have express written permission from a parent or legal guardian before You may use this Site. If PopFlash learns that it has collected or received Personal Information from a child under 13 without express written verification of parental consent, We will delete that information.If You believe PopFlash might have any Personal Information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at support@popflash.site.

**Recourse**

If at any time You believe that PopFlash has not followed the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy, please let us know by emailing us at: support@popflash.site. We will make reasonable efforts to identify and correct any problem.

**Changes**

PopFlash reserves the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time, without notice to You. From time to time, We may use Personal Information for new uses not previously disclosed in this Privacy Policy. If We do change this privacy policy, We will post the changes on the Site, and if the changes are significant, a more prominent notice will be made, including possibly an email notification.We encourage You to review this Privacy Policy each time You visit Our Site to make sure You understand Our current policy on collecting and using Personal Information. Your continued use of the Site signifies Your acceptance of any changed terms.

**Limitation**

It is PopFlash’s intention that this Privacy Policy apply only to PopFlash’s online data retention and collection activities. The Policy does not apply to any offline practices of PopFlash.

**Links**

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by PopFlash. Other websites (including those that We may now or in the future link to) may have their own privacy policies. PopFlash has no responsibility for or control over the information-collection practices of such third-party websites.

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If You choose to visit PopFlash.site, Your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and Our Terms of Use Agreement, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, application of the law of the State of New York and venue for all disputes in New York, New York.

We may amend or revise Our Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use Agreement and therefore You need to check Our Site and specifically Our Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use Agreement frequently to see recent changes.Unless stated otherwise, Our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that We have about You and Your account.

**Questions or Concerns**

If You have any questions or concern about privacy at PopFlash.site, please contact us at [support@popflash.site ](mailto:info@LolClass.com) with a thorough description, and We will try to resolve it.

Last Revised April 22, 2016
